Von Drehle, David; Papers apap213
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Jent/Miller - Fitzgerald, 1979-1980; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 11-12)
- Jent/Miller - Fritts, 1987 (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 13)
- Jent/Miller - Frye, 1979; 1981; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 14-16)
- Jent/Miller - Hubbard, 1979; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 17-19)
- Jent/Miller - inmate testimony, 1987; Undated (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 20-21)
- Jent/Miller - Morris McDonald, 1987; Undated (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 22)
- Jent/Miller - motions, 1987 (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 23-24)
- Jent/Miller - new trial battles, 1988 (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 25)
- Jent/Miller - notes, Undated (Box 5 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 26)
- Jent/Miller - own letters, 1982 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 1)
- Jent/Miller - police investigation, 1979-1980 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 2)
- Jent/Miller - release, 1988; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 3)
- Jent/Miller - sources, 1985; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 4)
- Jent/Miller - Suzie (Ruby) letters, 1985; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 5)
- Jent/Miller - Tricaine/Bennett, 1979; 1986; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 6-7)
- Justice, Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 8)
- Juveniles, 1986-1987; 1989; 1990 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 9)
- In re: Kemmler, 1889 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 10)
- Kendall, David [Attorney], 1990; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 11)
- Kennedy, Edward F., 1992 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 12)
- Knight, Thomas (Askari Muhammad), 1980; 1982; 1984; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 13)
- Lambrix, Michael, 1988; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 14)
- Last meals, 1985; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 15)
- Legal Defense Fund, 1990 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 16)
- Legal Defense Fund - strategy, 1977 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 17-18)
- Lethal Injection, 1979; 1991 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 19)
- Lewis, Dorothy O., 1985; 1991-1992 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 20)
- Lewis, Robert (Bobby), 1978-1982; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 21)
- Lockett v. Ohio, 1977 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 22)
- Lockhart v. Mcree, 1986; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 23)
- Long Gap, 1980-1984; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 24)
- Magee, Doug, 1980; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 25)
- Mail/feedback, 1988-1989; 1994; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 26)
- Manuscript -Among the Lowest of the Dead, Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 27)
- Marky, Ray, ca. 1991; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 28)
- Martinez, Bob, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 29)
- McClesky v. Kemp, 1984-1986; 1991; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 30)
- McCray, James (Doug), 1978; 1982-1983; 1991; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 31)
- McRae - cases/moratorium [Judge], 1967-1972; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 32)
- The Miami Herald, 1979 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 33)
- Nelson, Walter "Mad Dog", 1986 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 34)
- Nelson, Wendy - L.O.V.E., 1981-1982; 1984-1986; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 35)
- New York, 1986; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 36)
- Op-ed - Anti, 1977-1981; 1984-1985; 1987-1990; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 37)
- Op-ed - Pro, 1977; 1981; 1984-1985; 1988-1990; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 38)
- Operation Besmirchment - Graham, 1980; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 39)
- Override, 1975; 1980; 1984-1986; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 40-41)
- Palm Beach P.D., 1982-1983; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 42)
- Palmes, Tim - case accounts, 1984 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 43)
- Palmes, Tim - execution, 1984 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 44)
- Palmes, Tim - litigation/clemency, 1982; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 45)
- Pitts, Freddie Lee, 1994; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 46)
- Polls/public opinion, 1967; 1971; 1981-1986; 1989-1993; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 47)
- Pro - Death Penalty, 1989; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 48)
- Proffitt, Chuck, 1979-1980; 1984; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 49)
- Proffitt - reaction, 1976; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 50)
- Proffitt v. Florida, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 51)
- Proportionality, 1979-1980; 1985-1986 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 52)
- Prosecutors, 1979; 1990 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 53)
- Race of victim - Florida, 1977-1978; 1981; 1991; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 54)
- Racial Justice Act, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 55)
- Radelet, Mike [Researcher], 1982; 1988; 1990; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 56)
- Raulerson, James - case accounts, Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 57)
- Raulerson, James - celebrations, 1985; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 58)
- Raulerson, James - execution, 1985; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 59)
- Raulerson, James - litigation/clemency, 1983 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 60)
- Raulerson, James - victim, 1980; 1985; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 61)
- Retardation, 1989 (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 62)
- Robinson, Steve [Judge], 1984-1987; Undated (Box 6 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 63)
- Sanity/mentally ill, 1980; 1984; 1986; 1990-1992; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 1)
- Schwarzschild, Henry, 1990; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 2)
- Senate Select Committee, ca. 1972 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 3)
- Series - notes, 1988; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 4-6)
- Sex - procreation, 1992 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 7)
- Shevin, Bob [Attorney], 1967; 1972; 1976-1978; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 8)
- Shriner, Carl, 1979; 1982; 1984 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 9)
- Smith, Jim, 1971; 1982; 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 10)
- Snurkowski, Carolyn [Attorney], Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 11)
- Songer, Carl, 1989 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 12)
- Sources, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 13)
- Spalding, Larry [Attorney], 1979; 1985; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 14)
- Spaziano, Joseph, 1993 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 15)
- Spenkelink - aftermath, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 16)
- Spenkelink - anniversaries, 1980-1981; 1989; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 17)
- Spenkelink - bio, 1977; 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 18)
- Spenkelink - block investigation, 1979-1981; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 19)
- Spenkelink - chronology, Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 20)
- Spenkelink - commentary, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 21)
- Spenkelink - context, 1979 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 22)
- Spenkelink - death watch, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 23)
- Spenkelink - execution, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 24)
- Spenkelink - family, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 25)
- Spenkelink - Fifth Circuit Court, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 26)
- Spenkelink - first warrant, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 27)
- Spenkelink - Florida Supreme Court, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 28)
- Spenkelink - general/character, 1976; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 29)
- Spenkelink - interviews, 1978; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 30)
- Spenkelink - last days, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 31)
- Spenkelink - legislature, 1979 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 32)
- Spenkelink - litigation/clemency, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 33)
- Spenkelink - memorials/funeral, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 34)
- Spenkelink - protests, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 35)
- Spenkelink - public reaction, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 36)
- Spenkelink - selection, 1979; 1990 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 37)
- Spenkelink - TV coverage, 1979; 1982-1984; 1986 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 38)
- Spenkelink - Thanksgiving brawl, 1978-1979 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 39)
- Spenkelink - warrant signed, 1979 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 40)
- Spenkelink - Warren Folks, 1981 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 41)
- Stano, Gerald, 1982-1983 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 42)
- Starke - Florida, 1979-1980; 1984; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 43)
- Steffens, Betty [Attorney], Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 44)
- Straight, Ronald - execution, 1986 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 45)
- Strategies - anti, Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 46)
- Streamlining, 1979; 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 47)
- Strickland v. Washington, 1983-1984 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 48)
- Sullivan - anniversary, 1984 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 49)
- Sullivan - case accounts/bio, 1973; 1980; 1983; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 50)
- Sullivan - commentary, 1983 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 51)
- Sullivan - execution, 1983; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 52)
- Sullivan - legal defense fund, 1983; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 53)
- Sullivan - litigation/clemency, 1979-1980; 1983; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 54)
- Sullivan - memorials, 1983; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 55)
- Sullivan - Pope, 1983 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 56)
- Sullivan - protests, 1983 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 57)
- Sullivan - writings/interviews, 1976-1983; 1991; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 58)
- Tafero, Jessie, 1977; 1982; 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 59)
- Testimony - Congressional records, 1988; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 60)
- Texas, 1980; 1982; 1986; 1988-1989; 1991 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 61)
- Thomas, Daniel - bio, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 62)
- Thomas, Daniel - execution, 1986 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 63)
- Thomas, Daniel - litigation/clemency, 1982 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 64)
- Thomas, Daniel - reaction, 1986 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 65)
- Tibbs, Delbert, 1978; 1982; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 66)
- Trop v. Dulles, 1957 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 67)
- Tucker, Ken [Attorney], Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 68)
- United States Supreme Court - cases, 1980; 1983-1988; 1990; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 69)
- United States Supreme Court - justices, 1979; 1983; 1986-1989; 1990; 1994 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 70)
- Vandiver, Margaret [Researcher], 1984; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 71)
- Vasil, George, 1977; 1979 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 72)
- Victims - survivors/families, 1981; 1983; 1985-1987; 1990; Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 73)
- Violence, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 74)
- Volunteers, 1983; 1990 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 75)
- Volunteer Lawyers Resource Center, 1989 (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 76)
- Von Drehle Notes from Harry Blackmun's Papers on Death Penalty Jurisprudence at the Library of Congress, Undated (Box 7 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 77)
- Washington, David - execution, 1984; Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 1)
- Washington, David - litigation/clemency, 1981; 1984 (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 2)
- Washington, David - remorse/bio, 1984; Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 3)
- Wax, Bill [Photographer], Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 4)
- White, Beauford - execution, 1987 (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 5)
- White, Beauford - litigation/clemency, 1978; 1984-1987 (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 6-7)
- Whitney, Dennis, 1968; 1971-1972; 1977 (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 8)
- Witt, Johnny Paul - case, Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 9)
- Witt, Johnny Paul - execution, 1985 (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 10)
- Witt v. Florida, 1980; Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 11)
- Wives/girlfriends, 1986; Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 12)
- Ziegler, Tommy, 1986; 1992; Undated (Box 8 (David Von Drehle Papers ), Folder 13)